aussiestockforums.com 2015-11-10

# Aussie Stock Forums - Privacy Policy

Aussie Stock Forums takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**When do we collect information?**

Aussie Stock Forums collects personal information when you register with us, when you use Aussie Stock Forums or the pages of certain Aussie Stock Forums partners.

Aussie Stock Forums automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Aussie Stock Forums cookie information, and the pages you request.

**What information do we collect?**

When you become a member of the Aussie Stock Forums website you will be asked for your current, valid email address along with a user name and a password of your choice. Once you have accessed the website you may be asked for your date of birth, hobbies, interests and any description of yourself you choose to give. You may, however, visit our site anonymously without joining.

Aussie Stock Forums automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Aussie Stock Forums cookie information, and the pages you request.

Aussie Stock Forums may collect information about your activities with us and with some of our business partners.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used for any of the following purposes:

To personalise your experience: Your information may help us to better respond to your personal needs.

To improve our website: We rely on information we receive from our members to improve all aspects of our website based on information and feedback we receive from our members.

To send you emails: Aussie Stock Forums from time to time may send its members emails which may include advertising material, site news or announcements.

Please note that members can choose to opt out of emails from Aussie Stock Forums any time by following the instructions at the bottom of the email. Please also note that if you choose to opt out of the emails your access to the forums will be restricted, as it is a condition of membership that you accept all emails from Aussie Stock Forums.

Aussie Stock Forums may also use your information for any of the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**Information Sharing & Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in the daily operation of our website, conducting our business, or serving you so long as those parties agree to keep your information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release may be appropriate to comply with law, litigation, enforce our site policies or protect ours or others rights, property or safety. No personally identifiable visitor information is provided to other parties for advertising or marketing purposes.

Your personal information will be transferred to any new company or organisation that may acquire or merge with Aussie Stock Forums in the future. In this situation, members will be notified of any such event before a transfer takes place.

**Cookies**

Aussie Stock Forums may set and access cookies on your computer. Other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages may set and access their cookies on your computer.

Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Aussie Stock Forums cookies.

**Confidentiality & Security**

Aussie Stock Forums limits access to personal information about you to employees, moderators or anyone who we believe will need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

**Changes To Your Account/Membership**

You reserve the right to cease your Aussie Stock Forums membership at any time. If you wish to cease being a member of the Aussie Stock Forums website please contact us and we will disable your account and all account information at your request.

Please be aware that by joining and continuing to use our website you consent to the above privacy policy.

Aussie Stock Forums may make changes to this policy. If we choose to make changes you will be notified of any significant changes by the email address you have provided and/or we will make an announcement on our website.

This policy was last modified on 18/04/2011
